sdccu.com 2004-06-10

# San Diego County Credit Union-Privacy Policy

|   
  
---  
|   
---  
|  | _SAN DIEGO COUNTY CREDIT UNION  
ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY_ |   
---|---  

**Our Commitment to Privacy**  

Welcome to San Diego County Credit Union's web site (the "Site"). San Diego County Credit Union is dedicated to providing you with products and services to meet your financial goals any where, any way, any time. Keeping your personal financial information secure and confidential is our utmost priority. We value the trust and confidence that you have placed in us and we will continue to protect your privacy.

For purposes of this Policy, the terms "we," "us," "our," "SDCCU," and "credit union" refer to the San Diego County Credit Union, S.D. E-Commerce, LLC, and all other affiliates of San Diego County Credit Union. "You" refers to you, as a user of this site. Our Privacy Policy (the "Policy") was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the highest-quality products and services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our members and partners. This statement will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our members' needs.

By using this Site, you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Policy. This Policy applies to individuals and we reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy, along with related procedures, at any time.

This Policy is designed to assist you in understanding: 

  * What personally identifiable information of yours is collected from you through the Site; 
  * How your personally identifiable information is used; 
  * With whom your personally identifiable information may be shared; 
  * What choices are available to you regarding the collection, use and distribution of your personally identifiable information; 
  * The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of your personally identifiable information under SDCCU control; and 
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in your personally identifiable information. 

**What personally identifiable information of yours is collected from you through the Site**  

SDCCU is the sole owner of the information collected on this Site. We will not sell, rent or license to, or share with, others this information in any way different from what is disclosed in this Policy.

In order to service your account and better understand your financial needs, we collect information from our users at several different points on our Site. That information is compiled from the following sources: 

  * Your registration to use different features on the Site; 
  * Surveys, applications and other forms filled by you; 
  * Various credit services; 
  * Use of cookies, as defined below, on the Site; 
  * Log files of the Site; 
  * Your transactions with us, our affiliates or others; 
  * Consumer reporting agencies; and 
  * Verifications of information you provide on an application or other forms. This may be obtained from your current or past employers, or from other institutions where you conduct financial transactions. 

**How your personally identifiable information is used**  

We use web site browser software tools such as cookies and web server logs to gather information about our Site users' browsing activities in order to constantly improve our Site and better serve our members. This information assists us to design and arrange our web pages in the most user-friendly manner and to continually improve our Site to better meet the needs of our members and prospective members. We may use these technologies to capture information about you.

We also use Site log files and IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

SDCCU may keep personally identifiable information you provide to us, along with information we collect from outside sources, so that we can offer you accounts and services better tailored to your financial needs.

The information you provide to SDCCU through online surveys and promotions on the Site will be used for internal marketing purposes, as well as for the development of new services and information on the Site. This information will remain confidential and will not be shared or sold to third parties.

We may also disclose nonpublic personal information about you as permitted or required by law. That may involve information in connection with a subpoena or similar legal process, fraud investigation or the recording of Trust Deeds (mortgages) in public records.  

**With whom your personally identifiable information may be shared**  

SDCCU may provide aggregate information about our members, sales, Site traffic patterns and related Site information to reputable third parties, but this information will not include personally identifying data, except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy.

SDCCU may share information we collect with companies that perform marketing or other services on our behalf or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements. These companies may assist us in processing transactions on your behalf, maintaining or servicing your account, fulfilling your service request or protecting the security of your financial records. These companies are contractually restricted from disclosing the information received to other third parties and are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing their services.

We may also share information collected with our affiliates to provide access to additional financial products such as insurance services. Our commitment to provide you with competitive products and services is also a promise to give you more financial service choices that may involve working with other companies.

From time to time, you may notice offers from outside companies advertised on our Site. To protect our members' privacy, SDCCU only works with companies that agree to maintain strong confidentiality practices.

We also take measures to select product or service providers that are responsible and offer privacy protections to their members. However, we cannot, and do not, make any representations about the practices and policies of these companies, and are not responsible in any way for how these companies use cookies or any other information you provide to them.

If you terminate your membership with SDCCU, we will not share information we have collected about you, except as may be permitted or required by law.  

**What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of your personally identifiable information**  

Occasionally, we may also use personally identifiable information that we collect to notify you about important changes to our Site, new services, and special offers we think you will find valuable. The lists used to send you product and service offers are developed and managed under our traditional corporate standards designed to safeguard the security and privacy of our members' personal information. If you desire not to receive these offers, please write to us at, San Diego County Credit Union, 6545 Sequence Drive, San Diego, California 92121. Or you may phone us at 1-877-SDCCU-4U (732-2848).  

**The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of your personally identifiable information under San Diego County Credit Union control**  

The security of personal financial information is very important to us and we take a number of steps to protect it. We limit access to personal and account information only to those SDCCU employees who need to know that information in providing products and services to you. We maintain procedural, electronic, and physical safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information. We also require affiliates with whom we do business to maintain strong confidentiality practices.

We utilize encryption/security software to safeguard the confidentiality of personal information we collect from you. 

Cryptography scrambles messages exchanged between your browser and our online banking server. Encryption happens as follows: when you go to the sign-on page for online banking, your browser establishes a secure session with our server. The secure session is established using a protocol called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) Encryption. This protocol requires the exchange of what are called public and private keys. Keys are random numbers chosen for that session known only between your browser and our server. After the keys are exchanged, your browser will use the numbers to scramble (encrypt) the messages sent between your browser and our server. Both sides require the keys because they need to descramble (decrypt) the messages when they are received. The SSL protocol not only ensures privacy but also ensures that no other browser can "impersonate" your browser, nor alter any information sent. You can tell whether your browser is in secure mode by looking for the secured lock symbol at the bottom of your browser window. 

The numbers used as encryption keys are analogous to combination locks. The strength of encryption is based on the number of possible combinations that a lock can have. 

As the number of possible combinations grows, it becomes less likely that anyone would be able to guess the combination in order to decrypt the message. Today's browsers offer 40-bit encryption or 128-bit encryption. Both result in a large number of possible combinations. Our servers are compatible with both, although we recommend the use of 128-bit capable browsers. [Click here](http://www.fortify.net/sslcheck.html) to determine the level of encryption that your browser supports. 

Emails that you may send outside the sign-on page for online banking, may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures will be in place prior to your transmitting the information. For that reason, we ask that you do not send confidential information such as Social Security or account numbers to us through an unsecured Email.

We provide a number of additional security features in online banking. Online banking will "timeout" after 15 minutes of inactivity. This prevents curious persons from continuing your home banking session in case you have left your PC unattended without logging out. Requests you make through the Internet are handled by our home banking server, which retrieves the information you requested from our mainframe via proxy-based firewall servers. These servers act as the intermediary between you and our mainframe computers.

When you submit your password, it is compared with the password we have stored in our secure data center. We allow you to enter your password incorrectly four times. If you enter your password incorrectly more than four times, your online banking account will be locked until you call us to reinitialize the account. We monitor and record "bad login" attempts to detect any suspicious activity, such as someone trying to guess your password. You play a crucial role in preventing others from logging on to your account. Never use passwords that are easy to guess. Examples of bad passwords are: birth dates, first names, pet names, addresses, phone numbers and social security numbers. Never reveal your password to another person or entity. You should periodically change your password in the Account Management section of Internet Branch.

Our corporate values, ethical standards, policies and practices are committed to the protection of member information. In general, our business practices limit employee access to confidential information, and limit the use and disclosure of such information only to authorized persons, processes and transactions.  

**How you can correct any inaccuracies in your personally identifiable information**  

If your personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), we will endeavor to provide a way to correct or update your personal data provided to us. These actions can usually be done in the Account Management section of Internet Branch. Alternatively, you can write to us at, San Diego County Credit Union, 6545 Sequence Drive, San Diego, California 92121. Or you may phone us at 1-877-SDCCU-4U (732-2848).  

**What Are cookies**  

"Cookies" are a feature of web browser software that allows web servers to recognize the computer used to access a web site. They are small pieces of data that are stored by a user's web browser on the user's hard drive. Information gathered through cookies and web server logs may include information such as the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at the Site, and the web sites visited just before and just after our Site. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one web page to simplify subsequent interactions with that web site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user's transactions on related web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from web page to web page and to complete transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized.

You are not obligated to accept a cookie from us, or any other web site, and may modify your browser so that it will not accept cookies at your discretion. Here are instructions on how to do this for Internet Explorer and Netscape browsers: 

If you do not wish to receive cookies from us or any other website, you can turn cookies off on your browser. If you are unsure how to turn cookies off on your browser, please check the "help" feature on your browser or email our Customer Support.

Some of our associated companies may themselves use cookies on their own websites. We have no access to, or control of these cookies, should this occur. 

No Data "Capture" with Planning Tools. SDCCU provides many planning tools on the Site to assist you in financial planning. When you use various planning tools on the Site, we do not capture the personal information you provide when using these tools.  

**Links**  

We are not responsible for practices employed by web sites linked to or from our Site, nor the information or content contained therein. This remains true even where the linked site appears within the parameters or window/frame of our Site. Often links to other web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to users of our Site. 

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Site to another web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other web site, including web sites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that web site's own rules and policies. Please read these rules and policies before proceeding.  

**Notification of Changes**  

If we decide to change this Policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are kept aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by email. Users will have a choice as to whether to permit us to use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy operating at the time the information was collected.   

**Children's Privacy**  

Our Site is not intended for use by children. We do not knowingly market to, nor solicit data from, children.

Click here for further information on terms governing use of this Site.   

* * *  
  
For further information on terms governing use of this Site,  
see San Diego County Credit Union's Terms of Use Agreement  
  |  |   
In compliance with Federal Banking regulation D, telephone and automated savings withdrawals will be limited per month to comply with the regulation. During any calendar month, you may not make more than six withdrawals or transfers to another SDCCU account of yours or to a third party by means of a preauthorized or automatic transfer or telephonic order or instruction. If you use automated methods to make transfers or withdrawals from savings, fewer than six telephone or Home Banking transfers or withdrawals are allowed. Automated methods include Overdraft Protection Transfers to checking accounts and Automatic withdrawals made through the Automated Clearing House (ACH) or preauthorized draft withdrawals (i.e., bill payment, insurance premiums).
